150m.com 2003-04-01

# Privacy Policy

|  **Privacy Policy**  
  
This is the web site of **0Catch**. 

Our postal address is 

252 N. Orem Blvd.  
Orem, UT 84057  
We can be reached via e-mail at [admin@0catch.com](mailto:admin@0catch.com)

For each visitor to any of our sites, our Web server automatically records only the consumer's IP address. We do not and cannot see the email address of our visitors.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes, and may be used by us for marketing purposes as well. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us or do not want us to share your address in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line, we will only use it for the purposes for which it was provided to us. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. Nevertheless, if you wish your information removed from our listings, please provide us with your name and phone number, and we will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

With respect to cookies: we use cookies to store visitors' preferences, to record session information (such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart), to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, or to customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of our advertising partners

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server, and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site, and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us email at the address provided above.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to the information that we have collected and that we maintain about them, which they can then have corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau.

| 
|  **Privacy Policy**  
  
This is the web site of **0Catch**. 

Our postal address is 

252 N. Orem Blvd.  
Orem, UT 84057  
We can be reached via e-mail at [admin@0catch.com](mailto:admin@0catch.com)

For each visitor to any of our sites, our Web server automatically records only the consumer's IP address. We do not and cannot see the email address of our visitors.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes, and may be used by us for marketing purposes as well. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us or do not want us to share your address in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line, we will only use it for the purposes for which it was provided to us. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. Nevertheless, if you wish your information removed from our listings, please provide us with your name and phone number, and we will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

With respect to cookies: we use cookies to store visitors' preferences, to record session information (such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart), to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, or to customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of our advertising partners

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server, and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site, and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us email at the address provided above.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to the information that we have collected and that we maintain about them, which they can then have corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau.

|
